Guide to the New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records, [ca. 1960-2011]
New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records
- Individuals A-Z
  - G-I
    - Gorwwitz, Shalom - Experimental TV Center (VA 90), c. 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 156)
      Grant application (undated, FY95) for Roots and Branchers and an unnamed project; letter of agreement
    - Gotanda, Philip Kan - Manhattan Theater Club, c. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 157)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for an unnamed project; letter of agreement
    - Gotlheim, Larry - Experimental TV Center(FE 88), c. 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 158)
      Grant application 1987-1988, 1988-1989 for Cantos de Oriol and Machete Gillette...Mama; supporting materials; letter of agreement
    - Gould - Harvestworks (A 10), c. 1984 (Box 11, Folder 159)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Tellus
    - Gray, Amlin and Sham Mosher- Studio Theatre School, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 160)
      Project description for The Dragon and biographical information on Amlin Gray
    - Gray, Ronald - Dancing on the Streets, Inc. (IN 90), c. 1997 (Box 11, Folder 161)
      Grant application FY97 for Shadows Tearing; supporting materials; final report 1997
    - Greczynski, Bolek and Finkelpearl - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council (MD 53), c. 1988 (Box 11, Folder 162)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for The D Train Project
    - Green, Vanalyn - Women Make Movies (VD 103), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 163)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Baseball and the Body; letter of agreement
    - Greenspan, David - Ne Renaissance Chamber Artist, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 164)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for an unnamed play; letter of agreement
    - Greytak, Sharon -, 1984-1998 (Box 11, Folder 165)
      Grant application (1984-1985, 1988-1989, FY94, FY96, FY98) for She's Got Great Legs, Broken Frames, The Love Lesson, and The Resilient Spirit letters of agreement
    - Griffen, George - Moving Image - Film Forum (VA 82), c. 1997 (Box 11, Folder 166)
      Grant application FY98 for About Face and Final Report
    - Griffin, Ada Gay (VD 93), c. 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 167)
      Grant application (1997-1988, 1988-1989) for Zami: A New Spelling of My Name
    - Grome, Sinom (VD 219), c. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 168)
      Grant application FY98 for John Kelly: A Constant Stranger
    - Grove, Kathy and Jeanne Silverthorne - Franklin Furnace (PA 66), undated (Box 11, Folder 169)
      Grant application (undated) for The Other Series
    - Grunberg, Slawomir, c. 1999 (Box 11, Folder 170)
      Grant application FY99 for About Maysles
    - Guarino, Robin - Women Make Movies (VE 103), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 171)
      Grant application 1990 for The Shooting
    - Gustafson, Julie - Alternative Media Information Center (VD 95), 1986, undated (Box 11, Folder 172)
      Grant application for (1986-1987 and undated) for Abortion: Across the Barricades; letter of agreement (1986 and 1989)
    - Miscellaneous fliers and event calendars, c. 1994-1998 (Box 11, Folder 174)
      Biographical materials on Tobe Carey; Video Production Grant information from the Niagara Council of the Arts (1998); New York Exposition of Short Film and Video information (1997); Meet the Makers at the Donnell Library Center (1997-1998); Paper Tiger Television Summer Schedule (1994)(
    - Miscellaneous fliers and event calendars, c. 1994-1999 (Box 11, Folder 175)
      Port Washington Library event fliers (1997); Rensselaer events (1997-1998); Finkelstein Memorial Library 19th International Film Festival (1998); Frederick Douglas Creative Arts Center Final Report (1997-1998); Foundation for Independent Video and Film events (1999); Checkerboard Foundation (1994); Yellow Ball Films Workshop (undated); Survival Guide to Cannes (1997), Celluloid Cave poster (1997)
    - Miscellaneous fliers and event calendars, 1988-1990, undated (Box 11, Folder 176)
      Show the Right Thing conference packet (1989); Rome Art and Community Center Film Series (undated)Effort Easy Over Blue - Synopsis (includes photo); The Beanstalk and Jack book (1988); The Second Century conference of the University Film and Video Association at Ithaca College (1990); photos of large and small auditorium for public event
    - Hahn, Alex - Experimental Television Center (VA 127) (IND), c. 1988-1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Grant application (1988-1989, FY95 and undated) for Dirt Site, On the Nature of Things and The Kircher Itinerary; letter of agreement (1988, 1990, 1995)
    - Halac, Jose - Haleakala, Inc. (EL 32), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Letter of agreement, Cv for Jose Halac
    - Halleck, Deedee and Penee Bend - Alternative Media Information Center (V69D), c. 1984-1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Grant application (1984-1985,, 1985-1986, 1986-1987, and FY99) for Peliculas: Archives of Latin American Conflict 1900-1940, Paper Tiger related project, and too soon for sorry
    - Hamada, Sachiko - Film Now Foundation (VN 105), c. 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Grant application (1988-1989, 1990) for The Nail that Sticks Up; letter of agreement; supplementary materials
    - Hammer, Barbara - Experimental Television Center (VD 89), c. 1991-1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Grant application (1988-1989,FY91, FY97, FY98) for Dr. Watson's X-Rays, Sanctus, an unnamed project, The Female Closet and Porn Doctor; letter of agreement (1996); Final Report form FY1997-1998
    - Hammons, David, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Project proposal for an outdoor sculpture in Harlem; letter of agreement (1982)
    - Hampton, Slide - Sixteen as One Music (JZ 33), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      final report form for orchestral piece, letter of agreement
    - Hammond, Jane - Exit Art (PA 67), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Grant application (1990) for a series of ten large oil paintings; letter of agreement
    - Harris, Craig, c. 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for musical score to accompany Heat; sample of work submitted form (undated)
    - Harris, Leslie - Women Make Movies (VN 82), c. 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Grant application (1990, FY92) for Just Another Girl on the I.R.T.; letter of agreement (1991)
    - Harris, Thomas Allen - Electronic Arts Intermix (VD 134), c. 1992, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Grant application (1992-1993, FY95) for All in the Family; letter of agreement (1995)
    - Harrison, Amy - Women Make Movies (VD 96), c. 1989, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Grant application for (1989-1990, FY91) for Art Guerrillas
    - Hatcher, Brower (6D6), undated c. 1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Project proposal for a sculpture project in Lake George, NY
    - Hartke, Stephen - Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center (CH 76), c. 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Grant application (undated) for a commissioned piece for the Music of Our Times series
    - Hauft Amy - Hallwalls (IO 75), c. 1986 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Grant application (1986-1987) for Hedge Row maze
    - Hauser, Fritz - Pauline Oliveros (JZ 53), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Grant application FY90 for Deep Drumming music composition
    - Havis, Allan - CSC Repertory (89-0586), c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      Grant application (c. 1989) for the play The Inspector General
    - Hays, Sorrel and Barbara Kristaponis - NYFA (CO 98), c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      Grant application c. 1990 for Pill Woo and House; supplemental material
    - Haynes, Todd - NYFA (VN 267), c. 1988, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      Grant application (1988-1989, 1990) for Poison
    - Heath, Jimmy (JZ 93), 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      Sample of work submitted form; biographical materials; correspondence
    - Heckel, Sally (VD 101)(VD 88)(FN 88), c. 1986, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      Grant application (1986-1987, 1989-1990) for Unspeakable; Publicity
    - Helfand, Judith - Women Make Movies (VD 136) (IND), c. 1995, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      Grant application FY95 for A Healthy Baby Girl; correspondence
    - Hellerman, William - Soundarts Foundation, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
      Sample of work submitted form; press release (1984); letter of agreement (1989)
    - Hemingway, Gerry = Parabola Arts Foundation, Inc. (CH 35), c. 1988, 1997, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
      Grant application (1988, FY 1997-1998, undated) for Polar, Aivilik, Troika and The Visiting Tank; sample of work submitted forms; supplemental materials
    - Hemphill, Julius - Composers Forum (CH 202), undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
      Sample of work submitted forms
    - Henry, Diana Mara - The Catskill Center of Photography, Inc. (Eph 65), c. 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for One-Room Schoolhouses of Ulster County
    - Henry, Janet - Jamica Center of Performing and Visual Arts (6E1), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for American Anatomy Tree Apron Installation; correspondence
    - Henson, Robert (VD 106), c. 1997-1989 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1988-1989) for Trouble Behind; letters of agreement (1987, 1988); IND application for Sun Going Down
    - Hera, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
      schematic
    - Hegt, Saskia - Arts Inc., c. 1988 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      Grant application (undated)for Nine Songs; letter of agreement (1988)
    - Henderson, Douglas -PS122 (E 155), c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      Grant application FY910 for Gounod Fault III musical composition
    - Heriza, Tony - Asian Ameican Dance Theater (VD 80), c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Rangelands and Narrative for The Day of the Howling Dog: The Return of the Warrior for the New York Council for the Humanities
    - Heurich, Armin - Squeaky Wheel (VN 117), c. 1987 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Scratching the Wall
    - Heyliger, Yvette - Frank Silvera Writers Workshop, c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Father's Day
    - Heyward, Julia - NYFA (CO 25), c. 1987, 1995, 1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1996-1997, undated) for Mood Thing and Carpet Bombs; letter of agreement (1995)
    - High, Kathy - Standby Program (VN 81) (IND), c. 1985-1987, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1991-1992) for Saint to Sinner and Underexposed: The Temple of the Fetus; letter of agreement (1987, 1991)
    - Hill, Candace (Mg 71), 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      Grant application (1987-1988) for Ebony Men Too publication; letter of agreement (1987, 1988)
    - Hill, Chris - Hallwalls (VA 83) (IND), c. 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      Grant application 1991-1992 for Amplified Conversations; letter of agreement (1992)
    - Hill, Gary - Experimental Television Center (VA 99), c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for URA-ARU (There is a Reverse? Back Side); letter of agreement
    - Hills, Henry - Segue Foundation (F70E), c. 1984 (Box 12, Folder 40)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for More Money
    - Hill, Prudence - Cine Qua Non (VD 111), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      Grant application for Three Women; letter of agreement
    - Hiller, Lejaren, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
      Sample of work submitted form; letter of agreement
    - Hinton, Carma - Long Bow Groupr, Inc. (VD 110), 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Abode of Illusion and letter of agreement (1989)
    - Hirsch, Shelley - Roulette (EL 56), c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 44)
      Grant application FY90 for Rhapsody in Paisley
    - Hirshorn, Harriet - Woman Make Movies (VD 111) (IND), c. 1990, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 45)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for The Disappearance of TiSoeur; letter of agreement (1990)
    - Ho, Fred - World Music Institute (JZ 33) (IND), c. 2000 (Box 12, Folder 46)
      Background material on Fred Ho; letter of agreement
    - Hoch, Danny - PS 122 (SO 32), c. 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 47)
      Grant application 1994-1995 for Pot Melting; Final Report form
    - Hochhausen, Bill - Arts Council of Rockland, Inc. (SC 192), c. 1988 (Box 12, Folder 48)
      Grant application FY89 for sculpture pavilion and shelter; letter of agreement
    - Holcomb, Robin - Gotham Dance (SD 48), undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
      Background material on Robin Holcomb
    - Holden, Barry - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, c. 1986, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 50)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Leavittation; progress report (1988)
    - Holder, Tracie - NYFA (VD 93), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      Grant application FY96 for Joe Papp in Six Acts; letter of agreement
    - Holland, Fred and Robbie McCauley - NYFA (PE 73), c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 52)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for What I Like About Us; panel comments; flier
    - Holland, Dave - New York Shakespeare Festival (J 101), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 53)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for New Jazz at the Public music composition
    - Holzer, Jenny - Public Art Fund (7-5), c. 1984 (Box 12, Folder 54)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Sign on a Truck; correspondence; project description materials
    - Hong, Yunah - Women Make Movies (VN 101), c. 1996, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 55)
      Grant application (FY96, FY99) for Four Dreams From Far Away and Between the Lines: Asian Women's Poetry
    - Hopkins, Budd, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 56)
      Grant application 1982-1983 for Sacred Spaces; letter of agreement
    - Hornbacher, Sara - NYFA (VA 126), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 57)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Seeing Double: Curating the Postmodern with Collins and Milazzo; project update materials with interview of the artist; letter of agreement; flier
    - Horowitz, Wayne - CSC Repertory Ltd. (ST 80), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Howard, Earl - Parabola (EL 34), c. 1987, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 59)
      Grant application (1987-1988, FY92) for Quantum and Assonance; letter of agreement
    - Hsia, Lisa - Asian Cinevision (VD 96), c. 1987 (Box 12, Folder 60)
      Grant application (undated, c.1987) for In the Year of the Boar
    - Hubbard, Jim - New York Gay and Lesbian Experimental Film Festival, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 61)
      Grant application FY92 for Death; letters of agreement
    - Hudlin, Reginald - New Museum, c. 1988 (Box 12, Folder 62)
      Grant application (1988-1989) for Reggies's Third World of the Soul
    - Huggans, Amy - Collapsable Giraffe (WS019), c. 1998 (Box 12, Folder 63)
      Grant application (FY1998-1999) for Chun
    - Hughs, Holly - PS122, c. 1992 (Box 12, Folder 64)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for No Trace of the Blonde
    - Humes, Immy - NYFA (VD 182), c. 1998 (Box 12, Folder 65)
      Grant application FY98 for Pot: The Movie
    - Hummert, Darleen Pickering - Just Buffalo Literary Center (WS020) (IND), c. 1998 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      Grant application 1998-1999 for Home Again, Home Again; final report form
    - Hunt, Melinda, c. 2001 (Box 12, Folder 67)
      Grant application FY01 for Hart Island: An American Cemetery
    - Hurlin, Dan - Red Wing Performing Group, Inc. (PW 27), c. 1996 (Box 12, Folder 68)
      Grant application 1996-1997 for The Shoulder; final report form
    - Hurwitz, Leo - Kineholistics (F 81D), c. 1984 (Box 12, Folder 69)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for John Brown: Man and Myth
    - Hutchinson,B./Gregory - Harvestworks (CO 91), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      leter of agreement for unnamed project
    - Hutton, Peter - Upstate Films (VE 104), c. 1996 (Box 12, Folder 71)
      Grant application FY96 for Study of a River
    - Hwang, David Henry - Dance Futures Foundation, c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 72)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for The Voyage
    - Hwang, Jason - Dance Theater Workshop (CH 49), undated (Box 12, Folder 73)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography of Jason Kao Hwang
    - Hyla, Lee - Quintet of the Americas (CH 84), c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 74)
      Sample of work submitted forms; panel comments (FY89)
    - Imbrie, Andrew - New Philharmonic of Riverside (OR 98), undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
      Grant application (undated) for a commissioned piano Concerto
    - Irwin, Pat - Eccentric Motions (SD 85), c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 76)
      Grant application (1988-1989) for unnamed project
    - Isay, David, c. 1997 (Box 12, Folder 77)
      final report FY 1997-1998 for Flight
    - Ives, Steven, c. 1999 (Box 12, Folder 78)
      Grant application FY99 for The Amato Opera 9
    - Ito, Genji - Yara Arts Group, Inc. (SC 37), undated (Box 12, Folder 79)
      Sample of work submitted form, CV for Genji Ito
  - J-M
    - Jaar, Alfredo - International Arts Relations, Inc. (X 67), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 80)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Introduction to a Distant World
    - Jackson, Issac - Audio Art, Fashion Moda, c. 1984 (Box 12, Folder 81)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for radio series
    - Jackson, D.D., 2000 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Jackson, Judith PS 122 (PE 81), c. 1988 (Box 12, Folder 83)
      Grant application 1988 for Huhbebah's House
    - Jacobs, Ken (FE 121), c. 1988 (Box 12, Folder 84)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for The Alps and the Jews
    - Jannuzzi, Angelo - Bronx Council on the Arts (VD 116), c. 1988, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 85)
      Grant application (1988-1989, FY97) for Songs from Sing Sing and Transformations
    - Jenik, Adriene - Alternative Media Information Center (CA 141), c. 1987 (Box 12, Folder 86)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Paper Tiger Television series
    - Jenkin, Len - Coney Island USA, c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 87)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for commissioned play
    - Jenkins, Leroy, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 88)
      Grant application (undated) for music commission; letter of agreement (1986); final report (1987-1988)
    - Jesionka, Henry - Hallwalls (VD 114), undated (Box 12, Folder 89)
      Grant application (undated) for Tesla
    - Jennings, Pamela - Women Make Movies, Inc. (NT 117), c. 1993-1997 (Box 12, Folder 90)
      Grant application (FY963, FY95, FY97) for The American Art Song Project, Solitare Dream Journal and Hocketing Across the MBONE
    - Johnson, Scott - NYFA (EL 39) (IND), c. 1986, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 91)
      Grant application FY92, letter of agreement(1986); undated application materials
    - Johnson, Sue, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 92)
      Panel comments and CV for Sue Johnson
    - Jonas, Joan - Performing Artservices, Inc, c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 93)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for The Laxdaela Saga
    - Jones, Jeffrey M. - En Garde Arts (PW 37), c. 1994 (Box 12, Folder 94)
      Grant application 1994-1995 for J.P. Morgan Saves the Nation; letter of agreement
    - Jones, Kristen and Andrew Ginzel - The New Museum (IO 88), c. 1986 (Box 12, Folder 95)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Triptych
    - Jones, Lisa - Friends of Davis Hall/Aaron Davis Hall (PW 36), c. 1994 (Box 12, Folder 96)
      Grant application 1994-1995 for Stained; Final report form
    - Jones, Philip Mallory - Experimental Television Center (VI 93)(IND), c. 1991 (Box 12, Folder 97)
      Grant application 1991-1992 for First World Order
    - Jost, Jon (VN 126), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 98)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Deseret formerly Killing Grounds; letter of agreement
    - Jubela, Joan - Educational Video Center (VD 98), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 99)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Teenagers; letter of agreement
    - Julien, Isaac - Gotham Dance (VE 103), c. 1998 (Box 12, Folder 100)
      Grant application FY98 for The Conservator's Dream
    - Kahan, Adam, c. 2001 (Box 12, Folder 101)
      Grant application FY01 for Splitting the Lobes
    - Kalin, Tom - Drift Distribution (VE 119)(IND), 1989-1994 (Box 12, Folder 102)
      Grant application (1989-1990, FY92, FY94) for Under Separate Cover, Swoon and Third Known Nest; letter of agreement (1993)
    - Kaminsky, Laura - Musicians Accord (CV 92), undated (Box 12, Folder 103)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography for Laura Kaminsky
    - Karpell, Linda (VD 127), c. 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 104)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Dreampaths: The Aboriginals of Australia; progress report
    - Katz, Leandro - NYFA (VN 112), 1985, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 105)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Mirror on the Moon; letter of agreement (1985, 1989); flier
    - Katz, Joel - Media Network (VD 161) (IND), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 106)
      Grant application FY95 for Peripeteia: Carrie Wagner's Travels; letter of agreement
    - Katz, Leandro - Millenium Film Workshop (VD 106), 1997, c. 1998 (Box 12, Folder 107)
      Grant application FY98 for Bedlam Days: The Early Days of Charles Ludham; letter of agreement
    - Kaul, Kavery - NYFA (VN 122) (IND), c. 1987-1994 (Box 12, Folder 108)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1990, FY94) for One Hand Don't Clap and Distant Raga; letter of agreement (1988, 1991, 1993)
    - Kaus, Bradley, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Kaye, Pooh - Eccentric Motions (VA 134), 1990, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 110)
      Grant application 1990 for The Mean Princess; letter of agreement; amendment
    - Kearns, Jerry - Exit Art (Ep 90), c. 1986 (Box 12, Folder 111)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for 10 diptych paintings
    - Kennedy, John - Essential Music (CH 43), undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
      CV for John Kennedy
    - Keydel, Julia - Goddard Riverside Community Center (VD 129), c. 1985, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 113)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Capitol Hall Story; correspondence
    - Kheehog, Nawang - River Arts Repertory (SC 45), undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
      artist's bio for Nawang Khechog
    - Kibbee, Kyle - Film News Foundation (VD 94), c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 115)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Tell Them not to Mention
    - Kilgore, John - Eccentric Motions (SD 41) (IND), c. 1992 (Box 12, Folder 116)
      Grant application FY92 for Bee's Knees and Wake Up Call; correspondence
    - Kim, Jin Hi - Experimental Intermedia Foundation (EL 54), undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
      Biographical information on Jin Hi Kim
    - Kincaid, Jamaica - Cycle Arts Foundation, undated (Box 12, Folder 118)
      brief biography
    - King, John, c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 119)
      Grant application FY90 for Bukowski Projectiles
    - Kirkwood, Neal, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - Klahr, Lewis - Haleakala (VA 25) (IND), 1986, 1989, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 121)
      Grant application (1986-1987, 1989-1990, FY96) for The Morning Films, Tales of the Forgotten Future and Whirligigs in the Late Afternoon; letter of agreement
    - Kliros, Hilary - Artist Space (MM 152), c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 122)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Body of Work (Women and Labor)
    - Klonarides, Carole Ann (CO 131), c.1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 123)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1988-1989, 1990) for Cascade Vertical Landscapes, AIDS/ SIDA PSA campaigns installation; MICA-TV; letter of agreement (1990)
    - Ksugi, Takeshisa - Composer's Forum (EL 81), c. 1987, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 124)
      Grant application FY92 sample of work submitted form; project description (c. 1987) for commissioned score to be part of a Cunningham/Cage dance piece
    - Klucevesek, Guy - Angelo Caponigra (SD 65), c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 125)
      Grant application FY90 for a commissioned score
    - Knight, Erik - Camera News (VE 126) (IND), c. 1994 (Box 12, Folder 126)
      Grant application FY94 for Dread Night Folk
    - Kobland, Ken - Haleakala (CO 105), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 127)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Radio/Video; letter of agreement
    - Kolb - 92nd/Barbara, undated (Box 12, Folder 128)
    - Kondek, Christopher - The Wooster Group, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 129)
      final report FY 1998-1999; letter of agreement
    - Kopple, Barbara - Cabin Creek Workshop Environmental Center, c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 130)